The last scream you hear will be your own.
Screamers is a horror, science fiction, war film directed by Christian Duguay.
SIRIUS 6B, Year 2078.
On a distant mining planet ravaged by a decade of war, scientists have created the perfect weapon: a blade-wielding, self-replicating
race of killing devices known as Screamers designed for one purpose only -- to hunt down and destroy all enemy life forms.
Colonel Hendricksson, played by Peter Weller.
Jessica, played by Jennifer Rubin.
Becker, played by Roy Dupuis.
Ace Jefferson, played by Andrew Lauer.
Landowska, played by Liliana Komorowska.
David, played by Michael Caloz.
Screamers is a 1995 science fiction horror film starring Peter Weller, Roy
Dupuis, and Jennifer Rubin, and directed by Christian Duguay.
The screenplay, written by Dan O'Bannon with a rewrite by
Miguel Tejada-Flores, is based on Philip K.
Dick's 1953 short story "Second Variety", and addresses themes commonly found in that author's work:
societal conflict, confusion of reality and illusion, and machines turning upon their creators.
The film received generally negative response from
critics at the time of its release.
A sequel Screamers: The Hunting, was released in 2009, to mixed reviews.
The film explores themes of man vs machine, alien planet,
struggle for survival, android horror.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.